Contact

blake.hanegan@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/blakehanegan-21447017 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Nursing

Cerner

Critical Care

Certifications

Midline Insertion

Critical Care Registered Nurse (CCRN)

Advanced Cardiac Life Support (ACLS)

Basic Life Support (BLS)

NIH Stroke Scale (NIH)

Blake Hanegan

House Supervisor, RN, BSN, CCRN at Our Lady of the Lake Ascension

Baton Rouge, Louisiana Area

Summary

Experienced Registered Nurse with a demonstrated history of working in the hospital & health care industry. Skilled in Medical-Surgical, Pediatric Advanced Life Support (PALS), Vital Signs, Intensive Care, and Advanced Cardiac Life Support (ACLS). Strong healthcare services professional with a Bachelor of Science in Nursing focused in Registered Nursing/Registered Nurse from Our Lady of the Lake College.

Experience

CR Bard - Europe, Middle East and Africa (EMEA) Independent Contractor April 2018 - Present (2 years 3 months)

Teaching/educating nurses how to place vascular accesses

St. Elizabeth Hospital House Supervisor/ICU Supervisor March 2016 - November 2018 (2 years 9 months) Gonzales, Louisiana

Baton Rouge General Medical Center Registered Nurse September 2012 - August 2014 (2 years) Burn Unit

Burn Unit- Mid City

Our Lady of the Lake Regional Medical Center 3 years 8 months

Registered Nurse January 2012 - August 2014 (2 years 8 months) Surgical Intensive Care Unit (SICU).

Nurse Technician

January 2011 - December 2011 (1 year)

Baton Rouge, Louisiana Area

Baton Rouge Physical Therapy-Lake Physical Therapy Technician January 2008 - December 2011 (4 years)

Education

Our Lady of the Lake College
Bachelor of Science in Nursing, Registered Nursing/Registered
Nurse · (2012 - 2013)

Our Lady of the Lake College
Associate of Nursing, Registered Nursing/Registered Nurse · (2010 - 2012)

Louisiana State University

Bachelor of Science (B.S.), Physical Therapy/Therapist · (2004 - 2007)